Guide to the Joan Jacobs Brumberg papers,1980-2014.
Brumberg, Joan Jacobs papers
- Series IX. Audio-Visual Material
  - The Body Project five minute video, no date; V-10449 (Box 16)
  - An interview with Janet Reno at Balch Hall, 2003-02; V-1086 (Box 12)
  - Home economics interviews, 2000-12; V-10487 (Box 12)
  - The Jewish Museum, Women's Words/UJA federation panel discussion, 1998-06; V-1088 (Box 12)
  - Joan Jacobs Brumberg, NBC Today, 1997-09; V-1089 (Box 12)
  - Joan Jacobs Brumberg, NBC Today, 1997-09; V-1090 (Box 12)
  - BBC Medicine Now, TR-8190a (Box 12)
  - Gastronomy conference, Food: American Culture, 1985; TR-8191a (Box 12)
  - Joan, TR-8192a (Box 12)
  - Brumberg tape, TR-8193a (Box 12)
  - Joan Jacobs Brumberg, 2004-02; TR-8194a (Box 12)
  - "Women, Appetite and Sexuality", Joan Jacobs Brumberg, TR-8195a (Box 12)
  - Joan on Lenny Copate, 1998-11; TR-8196a (Box 12)
  - "Fresh Air", TR-8197a (Box 12)
  - Kuow's Weekday: The Body Project, 1997-10; TR-8198a (Box 12)
  - Joan Brumberg on anorexia nervosa, TR-8199a (Box 12)
  - Joan Brumberg, TR-8200a (Box 12)
  - Joan Jacobs Brumberg, TR-8201a (Box 12)
  - Joan Brumberg, TR-8257a (Box 12)
  - The moral majority and evangelicalism in America, TR-8258a (Box 12)
  - WAMC's Alan Chartock in conversation with Joan Jacobs Brumberg, 2004; CD310 (Box 12)
  - WAMC's Alan Chartock in conversation with Joan Jacobs Brumberg, 2004; CD311 (Box 12)
  - Joan Jacobs Brumberg's interview, 2004-03; CD312 (Box 12)
  - Kansas Charley: A Tale of Life and Death in the Old West, Did Justice Prevail?, 2004-02; CD313 (Box 12)
  - ATC hour 1, 2002-12; CD314a (Box 12)
  - ATC hour 2, 2002-12; CD314b (Box 12)